Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative files, 1967-2014; 1986-2014; Accession 2016-A-073
  - Bass Professors, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Beineke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bellonci Exchange, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Berkeley Fellows, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - BMS Agreement, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - BBS (Biological Biomedical Sciences), 1995 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Bouchet Dedication Background, 1998 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - BNL Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Edward Bouchet, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Buckley Ammendment, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - GS Calendars, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Grad. School Campaign, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Thomas Appelquist, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Relations and Development Working Folder, 1994-2004 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - AAU, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Admissions, 1995-2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Director, Office of Faculty Affairs, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - AGS, 2005 September 24-26 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Alternate Group, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Canon Nat'l Parks Science Scholars Program, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Career Services, 1996-2003 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Career Services Workshop, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Grad. Career Services, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - CAREW Committee, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Center for Globalization, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - CGIAY, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - CIRA, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Combined Awards, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Commencement, 2003-2014 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Communications Issues, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - CCR, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - CONACYT Consejo Nacional de Ciencia y Tecnol., 2002 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Congress of Neurological Surgeons, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Cooperative Research Committee Meeting, 2001 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Grad School Report, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Corporate Partners Program, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Council on Governmental Relations, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - CGS Communicator, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - CGS - Enrollment Figures, 1986-2005 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - CGS Ph.D. Completion Program, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - CGS, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Wilbur Cross, 2007 May (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Wilbur Cross Fall, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Wilbur Cross, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Wilbur Cross, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Wilbur Cross, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Wilbur Cross, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Wilbur Cross, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Wilbur Cross Selection Committee, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - In the Company of Scholars, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - In the Company of Scholars, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - In the Company of Scholars, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - In the Company of Scholars, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - In the Company of Scholars, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - In the Company of Scholars, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Drop Out and Stretch Out - John Perry Miller, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Council of Graduate Schools, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - CGS General Information, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Cowles Foundation Interviews, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Campus Crime, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Admissions, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Admissions, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Admissions, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - AAAS Handbook, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - AAAS, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - ACES, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 2-4 Project, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Affirmative Action, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bjorn Akselon: Ice House Design, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Career Services, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - McDougal Center, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Teaching Fellow Prep, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Affairs Briefing Materials, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Yale Alumni Magazine, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - YAM Editors Search, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Yale Law Report, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Yale Medicine, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - YAM Board Meeting, 2002 October 16 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - YAM Board Meeting, 2002 April (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - American Academy of Distinguished Students, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Amer. Council Learned Societies (Grants Fellowship), 1999 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Yale Animal Resources Center, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Art Gallery, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Arts Council, 2004-2006 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - AAU (Assoc. of American Universities), 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - AAU Disciplinary Programs, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - AAU Study Visit, 2002 April (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - AAU, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - AAU Washington Report, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - AAU Interdisciplinary Planning Group Washington, DC, 2002 June 26 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Sterling Fellowship, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Whiting Fellowships, 2000-2014 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Folger Insitutute, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Flasco, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Fortunoff Video Archive, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - General Counsel, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - General Counsel, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Confidentiality of Student Records, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Conflict of Interest/Commitment, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Info. Processing Review Committee, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Gerber, 2000-2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Globalization GV, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - GESO Student Petitions, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Governance, 1999-2004 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Whitehall, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - GPSS, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - GPSS, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - GPSS, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Grad Prof. Student Senate, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - GPSS, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Financial Report, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - GRE, 1994-2002 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - GSA, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Annual Report, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - GS Annual Report, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - GSA, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - GSA, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - GSA, 1965-1999 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - GSA Charter, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - GSA Charter Review Spring, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - GSA Town Mtg., 2002 February 27 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - GESO, 2006 December 12 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence re: Unionization, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - GESO Press, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - GESO Mtg., 1998 July 29 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - GSAS Grad Student Council, Harvard, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Reports on Grad. Education, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Graduate Program Review, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Grad Students Non-Disclosure Info, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Graduate Student Meetings, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Grad School History, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Students' Grants Prizes, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - HGS Student Information, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Graduate School, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Graduate Teaching Center, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - GSA, 2002-2004 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - HGS Building Activities, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - HGS Space, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - HHMI, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Honorary Degree Nominations, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Keys, 1970-81 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Housing, 1992-2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - HGS/HHS Issues, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - HFSP, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Research Grant Applications (short), 2002 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - IRA Charitable Rollover, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Red Cross - Casino Night Fundraiser, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Immigration, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Igert Proposal, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Univ. Committee on INFO. Technology, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Student Insurance, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - INP Ethics, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Interdisciplinary Programs, 1991-2004 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - International Students, 1992-2003 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - International Exchanges, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Int. Teaching Assistants Program, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Inter-University Centre Dubrovnik, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Investigator Track Review, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Konstanz, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Jaynes Committee Report, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - The Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Lanugage/ESL/Writing Tutors Instruction, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Fireside Chats, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Law School Proposal, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Lamar Center, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Folger Library, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Mace - Graduate School, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Marie Curie Celebration, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Matriculation, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - 0, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - McDougal Center 5th Year Anniversary, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - McDougal Center, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Medical School Term Appts. And Promotion, 1999 April 21 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Yale School of Medicine, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Business (Med. School), 1999 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Mellon, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Mental Health Wellness, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Mentoring Awards - Grad St., 1999 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Mentoring Awards - Faculty, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Mory's, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Peabody Museum, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Nomination for Nobel Meeting, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - NRC, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - National Research Council, 1992-2001 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - NELC, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - NIH, 1995-2003 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - NINDS Council, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - NNDS Washington, DC, 2002 September 11-13 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - NISE (Nat'l Institute for Science Education), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Northeastern Association of Graduate School, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - NYAS Letter Agreement, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Orientation Internal. Students, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Staff Seaeches Outside of Yale University (1 of 2), 2000-2004 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Staff Seaeches Outside of Yale University (2 of 2), 2000-2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Placement Data, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Peking Univ. Exchange, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Pfizer Correspondence, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Yale Police/Facilities Reports, 1992-1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Portraits, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Postdoctoral Notes, 1993-2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Postering, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - President's Committee on Racial Ethnic Harrassment, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Presidential Appts., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - GS Press Clippings, 2002 January-June (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - GS Press Clips, 2001 July-December (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Office of Public Affairs, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Dean Hockfield's Press, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Office of Public Affairs, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Press Releases Graduate Student Issues, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Porter Field Prizes, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Programs and Policies, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Programs, 1998-2007 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Programs Policies, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Programs Policies Catalog, 1994-1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Reaccreditation, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Registrar, 1999-2003 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Goody/Clancy Meeting Memo, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Residential Colleges, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Responsive Ph.D. Fall Roundtable, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Responsive Ph.D., 2002 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Responsive Ph.D., 2004 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Retirements, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Retirements, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - "Right to Privacy", 1998 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Robert Harper-Mangels Review, 2009 Spring (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Jon-Old Res Acct Invoices/Receipts, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Yale Science Forum, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Security-Hillis Letter, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Self Study Data, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Silliman Bicentennial Committee, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - National Univ. of Singapore, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Sloan Foundation (Michael Teitelbaum), 2004 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Smoking Policy, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Smithsonian, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Social Science Club, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Assist Dean - Science, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Associate Dean Search, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Graduate School Surveys, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Staff Activity Reports Spring, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - McDougal Center/Student Life, 1998-2004 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Senior Staff Standing Meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Lingua Franca Analaysis Shankar, UMA, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Yale Faculty Teaching, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Summer Funding, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Teaching Fellow Program, 2002-2004 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Teaching Fellows/Peer Tutor Program, 2006 March (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Teaching Fellows, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Dissertation Fellowship Teaching Policy, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Teacher's Institution, Yale-New Haven, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Teaching Issues, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Tercentennial (1 of 4), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Tercentennial (2 of 4), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Tercentennial (3 of 4), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Tercentennial (4 of 4), 2001 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Government, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Yale College Undergraduate Reg., 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - University Health Services, 1994-2003 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - YUHS, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - UHS Fall Health Holds, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - U.C. Grad Students, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Unionization, 1997-1999 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - US Department of Education, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - WAT, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Unviersity Appts., 1999-2004 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - WFF Report, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Women's Issues, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Diversity - Gender, 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Women in Science, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Women in Science at Yale WISAY, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Women in Science, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Woodrow Wilson Responsive PhD Roundtable Spring, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Responsive PhD, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - YCIAS - Ethics and Int. Affairs Search, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Political Philosophy Search, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - YCIAS - Middle East Seach, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - YCIAS Appointments, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - YCIAS International Dist. And Finance Search, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - YCIAS, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - YCIAS, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - YCIAS Executive Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - YCIAS Faculty Research Grants, 1999-2003 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - YCIAS Annual Report, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Yale Center for International and Area Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Yale Club of New York, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Yale Club of New Haven, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Yale Club Scholars, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Budget records, 1969-1996; Accession 2016-A-069
  - Accounting transfers, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Admissions
    - Proposed rates and policies, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Statistics and summaries, 1978-1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Summaries, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alumni fund, 1969-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Budget comparisons, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Budget closings, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Budget data and correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Budget meeting data, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Budget meeting notes, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Budget notes and data, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Budget presentation
    - 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Budget problems-mid stream corrections, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Budget projections
    - 1975-1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Budget proposals
    - General, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Enrollment, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Real income, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Stipends, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Budget reports-actual and comparisons, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Budget studies, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Budget summaries, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Budget transfers
    - 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Requests, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Budget work pages, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence
    - 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Commitment projections, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Data entry methodologies, Undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Departmental transfers, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Endowment fund-estimated income and proposed expenses, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - List of endowed fellowships for reporting, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Endowed fellowships
    - 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Enrollment data, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Fellowship budgets and financial projections, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Fellowship budget proposals
    - 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 43-44)
  - Fellowship establishments, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Fellowship stipends
    - 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Stipend studies, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The relation of teaching assistantships to fellowship support, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Financial aid summary tables cumulative loan study, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Heinz-Yale scholarship fund, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Human/Social Science relativities, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Incoming class analyses, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Loans/Indebtedness, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - OB/OR budgetary effects, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Operating budgets, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Operating budgets-correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Operating budgets-notes and correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Operating statements, 1977-1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Plans for other graduate schools, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Problems, 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Real income, 1982-1988 (Box 2, Folder 19-21)
  - Real tuition income report, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Real tuition income study, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Rents, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Stipend projections
    - 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Stipend report, 1982-1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Student aid projections, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Student support and tuition paid, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Tuition fellowships, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Tuition income and fellowship expenditures, 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Tuition projections
    - 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - University fellowship budgets, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Year-end amounts, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 42)